# **Andrew R. Clark**

#### **BC** Student

Address Chestnut Hill, MA, 02467

Phone (952) 237-5461 **E-mail** clarkui@bc.edu

LinkedIn linkedin.com/in/andy-clark3

**WWW** github.com/aierus

**WWW** andyrclark.com

Energetic and diligent student with a desire to broaden horizons and explore the market through job experience. Experience in the medical sector has helped develop succinct and high-quality communication skills, as well as stressing the importance of proper procedure and documentation. Consistently working on personal projects with coding skills and a passion for automation. Always learning and readily teachable.

## **Work History**

#### 2020-05 - 2020-08

#### **EMT**

Safe Care Ambulance, Old Bridge, NJ

- Responded to medical emergencies alongside paramedics to treat and support patients in need
- Provided patient care to ill and injured patients during transport
- Consistently instituted best practices and appropriate emergency therapy needed to improve quality of life

#### 2019-12 - Current

## **Continuing Education Coordinator**

Boston College Emergency Medical Services, Chestnut Hill, MA

- Responsible for planning and scheduling 5 continuing-education classes per month
- Submit lesson plans to Office of Emergency Medical Services for approval
- Conferred and resolved education-related issues and problems with students, parents and school officials.

#### 2018-05 - 2018-08

### **Veterinary Assistant**

Westfield Veterinary Group, Westfield, NJ

- Shadowed Dr. Ben Doyle, assisted in performing exams such as initial assessment and disease screening.
- Provided exemplary customer service to owners, answering animal health questions and sharing positive animal care practices.
- Cleaned and disinfected exam areas, equipment and kennels to prevent spread of disease, control odors and maintain a healthy environment.

## **Skills**

EMT-B Certified (RWJ Hospital)

HTML, CSS

Python, Java, OCaml



Excellent

Excellent



Excellent

## **Education**

2019-09 - Current Bachelor of Science: Computer Science

Boston College - Chestnut Hill, MA

2015-09 - 2019-05 High School Diploma

Peddie School - Hightstown, NJ